Sakira Ishiyama of Juice-Juice
Here we go. This time I'll be talking with Kisaki Ebata of Juice-Juice,
and Sakira Ishiyama of Juice-Juice.
This is a program that goes behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the up-front group.
We will show you the process of recording, rehearsals, and other production processes.
First of all, let's take a look behind the scenes at the two MCs.
I, Emada, went to Ishikawa Prefecture for the first time the other day on our current spring tour,
At the end of the concert, I had Kanazawa Curry for the first time, and it was really delicious,
It was so good that I ate it for the first time after the concert, but I didn't have much time because it was the end of the concert,
I was like a food fighter and everyone was eating like this in a hurry,
I remember that it was my first time in Ishikawa, and this concert was a new challenge for me,
This concert is also my first challenge, so I hope everyone will come to see it because it is very attractive and fun.
I hope everyone will come to see the concert. I had Kanazawa curry, but it came with a cutlet, and I was told that if I added it, I could make it into a cutlet curry,
I was in a hurry so I couldn't make it into a curry with pork cutlets, but did you make it into a curry with pork cutlets?
I had a big plate like this, but they put it in a bowl like this, and I ate it in a hurry.
It was so delicious that I would definitely like to try the curry with pork cutlet next time.
And I, Ishiyama.
It was the first time for me to participate as Juice Juice in the Hina Fest held the other day, and the rehearsal was so hard.
We had to fit the big stage of Makuhari Messe into one rehearsal space, a rehearsal place, and a studio,
The stage was so large that we had to fit it all into one rehearsal space, a rehearsal hall, and a studio.
I put it down. So you don't even know if you are looking forward or backward until you are on stage.
There were a lot of things that I didn't know until I was on stage,
I was wondering if I would be okay on stage,
I remember that I was having so much fun that my nerves were dissolved and I was so happy that I could fly off the stage.
That's right. It was the first day for Sakura-chan too,
I think Sakura-chan worked really hard on her first day.
Thank you very much.
Let's start with the new album.
Beyonce, In the night sky where you can't even draw a dream
Making of the music video shooting
We are very happy to present to you the making of the music video for Beyonce's newest single, which was released on April 12.
Please take a look at the making of the music video for "In the night sky where you can't even draw a dream.
Thanks for watching this video.
See you in the next video.
Good morning.
Oh, they are all cute.
They are cute. Really.
Really cute.
Today is the music video shooting for "In the Night Sky When You Can't Even Dream.
I'll be by the room.
I'm going to play.
This time I'm going to sing while playing,
It's a little difficult to play while singing,
I'll practice.
I'll do my best.
I'll stay awake in the night sky where I can't even draw a dream
Someday I'll meet you while humming my favorite melody
I want to tell you how much I love you
I won't let you lie down.
When you were born yesterday
I came hand-tied Lovely
That's right. I don't know why at all yet,
It's going to be kind of gorgeous with piano and balasobandha, isn't it?
The soundtrack is gorgeous, too.
I think it's going to be very powerful.
Let's go beyond! Thank you very much!
Thank you very much!
I won't let you have a night sky you can't draw
So many stars love you
I love you
I can't paint anything
Even when I can't believe it
I was born on such a beautiful star
Don't forget
Thank you. I'm sorry.
Take care Bye Bye
On the edge of a word
Full of thoughts I held them all in my arms
I love you baby
Oh, I'm so excited.
I'm listening to the amazing live sound,
It's so cool.
It's a miracle we're sharing the song at first.
Lalala...
We are wearing costumes that are based on the concept of looking like we are having a recital,
They all look a bit ladylike and noble.
What do you think?
You don't see many Beyons like this.
I've been to a lot of Beyoncés,
I have seen many Beyons, but this music video made me feel that there are many Beyons that I have not seen yet.This music video made me realize that there are a lot of Beyoncés that I have not seen yet.
Okay, let's go to the show. Please do me a favor.
I love you for always living your life to the fullest
Even dreams can't come true, the moment you're here now
That you were born as you
For a long, long time
It only happens once.
For it's a beautiful thing
Yes, cut!
The rhythm was choreographed at a pitch tempo, so the choreography was based on the motif of renewal, or rather, it incorporated a lot of renewal,
So there are also choreographies in which the dancers form a single line and go around together in 3, 3, so it is quite challenging.
It's not very athletic. So the dance shots this time did not make me sweat or anything,
The dance shots are not so much about sweating, but about using one's head in many ways, such as having to keep in step with the person next to you, or stepping out with the right foot first,
In a different sense, it is a different kind of challenge.
We are all going to ride on the back of the whale.
Thank you very much.
Please turn around.
Done.
Yo, start.
He said it's good.
Then we'll all see.
Where?
Cut.
Okay, cut.
Okay, let's do it.
Greedy.
Greedy?
Here you go.
Shall we go?
Someday in your time
You and I will sing a song together tomorrow
I want to live.
I want to sing to you tomorrow.
I want to live
Someday with you
I want to sing a song with you tomorrow
I want to live
Thank you very much!
The filming has been completed.
We spent quite a long time filming this time,
The brass band played in this music video, and the rest of it was a rare opportunity to see some CGs in Beyonce's music video,
The music video had a brass band, and there was some CG, which is rare in Beyonce's music videos,
And there was also a lot of dancing,
In the past Beyonce's music videos, there have been many times when several people sing together or take cuts,
In the past Beyonce's music videos, there have been many times when only a few people sang or danced together,
I'm looking forward to seeing how the music video will turn out when it is completed,
I'm looking forward to seeing how the song turns out when it's finished, and I think it's attractive because it has Beyoncé-like qualities, but it also has parts that are not Beyoncé-like,
I hope that this song will bring hope to many people,
I hope that this song will give hope to many people and encourage them to work harder in the future after listening to Beyonce's songs,
I hope that this song will help many people to have hope, or to listen to Beyonce's songs and think about doing more in the future, or to have dreams and challenge themselves in various ways,
I am really looking forward to seeing how the music video is going to turn out,
I hope everyone will watch the music video as much as possible.
I hope everyone will watch the music video as much as possible, and I will put my heart and soul into each and every performance so that people will love the music as well.
Thank you very much.
When I first heard the song "Yume wo nakurenai yozora ni" (I can't even draw a dream in the night sky), I thought it was a picture book,
There is a picture book, and a small child reads the picture book,
The child reads the picture book and imagines the world.
I have an image that this song is the music of that world,
I already love this song, and I would be happy if I could cover it someday,
I was more impressed by Beyoncé's performance and the way she sang,
I was more moved by Beyonce's performance and the orchestra's performance through the screen,
I hope to hear this song again in various places.
When I heard this song for the first time, I wondered why it was like a musical or a picture book,
I felt that there was a story in each song,
When I saw the music video for the first time, the whale scene left a great impression on me,
I was watching the making of the music video now,
I was wondering how they filmed that scene,
I had no idea that it was shot at double speed, and I thought it was a very interesting part of the film.
This is the making of the making of the music video for Beyonds Yumeno Dakurenai Yozora ni.
New single "Yume to sake no dakurenai yozora ni" is now on sale!
Sounds like a lot of work, take a breather.
Here is the next one. Akari Takeuchi's first solo exhibition, high school dance close-up video
It is being held from Saturday, April 15
Apkami camera closely followed Akari Takeuchi's first solo exhibition "High School Dance" at Angulum!
Please take a look!
Thank you for watching!
Auto Blog
Oh, wow!
If it dries like this, it'll probably take an hour to dry.
So when you decorate it here like this...
I'm sure you mean decorate like this.I'm sure you mean decorate like this.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'll dry myself out.
It's okay.
Linlin looks better. The balance.
I prefer the best.
Wada-chan is better?
No? Lela?
Lela's part.
Today is a preparation day.
For my solo exhibition.
I asked my assistant, Linlin, to come over today.
Linlin was actually off today.
I called her on short notice and she came downstairs.
I was still sleeping when Keiji called me.
I woke up from sleep with a sore arm.
I was brushing my teeth.
I'm working on something right now,
Ange's block?
When I say "Ange's block," I mean like a bird.
There is a corner for Ange,
We decided on the layout together,
I was sure to put Rin-Rin in the middle.
It was a privilege to be here today.
And I also put some of my past works there.
She also helped me to find some places that I wanted to see,
I'm grateful for that.
It's my birthday flower to come here,
Just because it says "birth flower" on it,
The works are lined up with a little playful spirit that those who notice it will notice and those who don't won't understand,
The works lined up here range from the early members of S/mileage to Yuki Hirayama, the newest member,
All of the members who have joined Ange up to now have written their birthday flowers on their birthdays here.
How many are there? So far.
That's a lot of people. I was surprised, too.
I thought it would be a good idea, but there are too many.
What?
Too many, I thought.
There are probably not more than a dozen or so.
It's quite a lot.
There are 20 or so that are going to be displayed here now,
It just says "birth flowers,
But in reality, this person doesn't say in such detail that this flower is my birthday month or that it is RinRin's. Only those who understand the flower will know,
Only those who understand can understand.
It's a little bit of a playful zone.
You have to remember the birthdays of the members.
That's right. You will never know. You might be like, "What's this?
I have to memorize 23 birthdays.
That's right. Then you'll understand.
You see, I like these schoolchildren because they are so cute.
Beautiful. Red.
This one is black.
There are various colors, and the other one is white.
It's so cute and I love it.
I really appreciate it.
That's about it.
Realistically, I'd say two or three months.
I think it was about two months.
We did it all at a fast pace.
We started all of this in February, and we started in March, or was it a month?
But I think I was working on it for about two months.
Even when I looked at the weekly schedule, I saw Takei-san, Takei-san, and so on.
It was terrible, wasn't it?
Preparation for private exhibitions, preparation for private exhibitions, preparation for private exhibitions.
Everyone was working all the time, even when they were off work.
So, really, it was the end of the year after the graduation announcement. The end of the year,
In January, we were working on various different jobs.
I guess I started at the end of January.
It's been too fast from then to today,
I wonder if I'm doing it right.
I don't know. I'm not sure.
I was just pretending that I had half a year left to go,
But I've been so busy that I've decided it's not a good idea.
I said I had half a year left, but it's only two more months.
That's too soon.
Too soon. I don't have much time.
This is the title,
This is the very first one I made, the very first one in the process of making this Koteo piece.
This is the work I made with my teacher Shujino, whom I had been studying with for a long time,
Yes. I came to her house and asked for her help,
She said she couldn't do it by herself,
I said I couldn't do it alone, and we worked together to make this piece.This is a piece of work that we thought up together.
At this time, the teacher made us a bowl of katsudon.
We worked hard while eating it.
And then there is that place.
Tomorrow, before everyone arrives, we will be interviewed,
The media will be there,
We will write a one-shot story there and exhibit it as is,
That's amazing.
I would like to do something terrible.
So, will I fail or will I succeed?
I'm asking God.
I'm really asking God.
I'm going to challenge tomorrow with the feeling of asking for help.
It's really cool. All of it.
It's super fun.
I don't know much about calligraphy,
But even I can enjoy it.
Really?
I think so.
I am glad to hear you say so.
If you like Yasun, you will enjoy it even more.
That's right.
Probably around here.
Here we go.
Ready?
Oh, it's good, it's good, it's good. It's done.
OK!
It's done!
《Loud applause》
《BGM》
The first calligraphy exhibition was held at the high school beauty salon.
I wrote a lot of works, and many of you have already seen them, and I am very happy that you were pleased with them, and I am relieved that we were able to hold the exhibition.
I'm filled with a sense of relief that we were able to hold the show, but there were so many works from my childhood and other things that I'd like to share with the audience.
I'm so happy that you could actually see the works from my childhood, and I'm so relieved to be able to hold this exhibition.
If you haven't come yet, I hope you will enjoy it, and if you don't plan to come at all, I hope you will come with a light heart just to show your face and take a peek.
If you've already been once, I'd be happy if you'd come again and again.
Now, I'd like to introduce you to Mr. Takiuchi's first solo exhibition, High School Dance. I'd like to introduce you to the background of the jacket photo of the album "Big Love" by Angerme.
The background of the album "Big Love", which is a jacket picture of Angulum, was written by Ms. Takiuchi, and the character "love" was really cool.
It was really cool, and I hope to be able to see her first move in person someday.
I thought it was wonderful that what I like to do leads to work, or that I can express what I am good at or what I like to do, and I personally would like to see it.
Akari Takiuchi's first solo exhibition, High School Dance, will be held at Seitoku Memorial Picture Gallery in Meiji Jingu Gaien until Sunday, April 23.
Please visit the venue.
Let's see the rest of the show together.
With Kisaki Karada of Juice-Juice,
and Sakura Ishiyama of Juice-Juice.
Here is the next one.
Tsubaki Factory Skip! Skip! Skip! Dance Lesson
From Tsubaki Factory's latest single, Skip! Skip! Skip! Dance Lesson from Tsubaki Factory's latest single "Skip!
Movement. Move.
Don't do this.
Align, align, move.
Let's start from the first minute.
Ready, go!
This time, all this.
Let's continue with the rust.
Let's hurry up and get going.
You see who's going to the right?
Those going to the right go around like this.
Those going left go this way.
Some people went the other way.
I'll hurry up.
Chote.
OK, let's get the chute from here.
From the side.
Just bend your knee at the knee already. Kick firmly, and then stop with the leg that stops the flex.
Then, bend the hips and knees firmly and trace, and then, "Pon," and since there is a hand, drop the left shoulder with the shoulder and raise the right shoulder very much like this.
This is how I want you to enter. Then, spin your shoulders around.
And then, fashionably, with the image of going up the side.
Like this.
Bend firmly and curl up the shoulder.
Now, here, too, spread your fingers, so the image of bending back.
Then, spin, crunch, buttocks, buttocks, and down, and you're good.
Now that it's better, you can come from here to here, firm.
Come to the point where you can extend all the way up to the knee.
Some people end up with, "Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
It's a little lame, so I bring it to this point.
And if the body is in front of the body, it doesn't look good, does it?
It looks like a robot.
That's why I'm going this way.
I'm going to add technology, technology.Technology, I'm going to put technology.
Side, I want you to shake it like that, so, uh, that's totally better.
Beautiful, beautiful, beautiful, and so on.
And then, I'm going to put this on your cheeks and forehead.
So, with that image in mind. On the cheeks and forehead.
And then spread it wide. This is not here. This way.
Then, make a face like, "Hmm? And make a little face like, "Hmm? And then, "Good luck with the point. And then, poof! Toward you.
Pang. And repeat, Talala, kick, kick, par. Do big buttocks and shoulders. Right.
This is boring here, so you have to put it down like this. Yes, that's how much you do. Then, side, up.
Then, tsun, tsun, tsun, tsun. Spread your legs apart, and then, with the cords, raise your hands, and pop.
Then, answer again. Hote tetai, tsun, tsun. Again, there are still people who have done this four times.
And here, it's a little too small. It's so small that at a live performance, it's hard to understand what you're doing, so you have to do it a little more.
I want you to shake your body in the same way, more. You can do it in your own way, like this, or you can do it twice,
You can do it with two swings, or three swings, and put a little more on. Let's try it with a sound. Let's try it with sound. Yes, let's try it with sound.
Side of push
Sorry for the abruptness, but I'll see you today.
My heart is beating so fast
even the top of the wind
I'm so happy to dance that I jumped up and down
Dance with me, dance with me, dance with me
The moment I can't open my mouth
I'm heading out on my own
hold on, koi ko ko, stop
Side, down
Five, three, up.
Twist.
Stop, stop.
Push, popper.
Down.
OK.
Thank you.
Oh, there it is! Nice swings! Oh, that's a little better!
Cool!
Yeah!
Better!
Hey, Asa, can I talk to you for a second? I was wondering if we could do a little back-swapping.
Kishi-chan can go first, right?
Why don't you go first, and then we'll go after Yamachan?
Maybe because they were together now, they used up all the distance.
How did you do it? Timing?
OK, let's have the V team!
Five, six, seven, eight.
I knew it when I hit it.
I hit it. Come on, just ed, per apocalypse, right?
8... we're going to be in the fave English language... and you're going to see it... in the coolest way possible.
I want you to look at it.
I'm going to walk with my legs twisted like this on purpose so that my legs and body don't go together.
I'm going to walk naked with my neck long.
tan, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Better now!
Twist to the fingertips!
Clean to the fingertips!
Decide clearly which direction you want to continue
Dance all the way to the end!
Put some power in it.
Oh!
Exaggerate and detail clearly
Clearly.
Start.
Oh!
This song "Skip Skip Skip Skip" is a very bright and fresh song that makes you feel like skipping.
The dances this time are not only cute but also have a little bit matured and charming.
There are a lot of dances that are not just cute, but also have a bit of maturity and sexiness to them, and that's how I feel about them.
There's a part where me, Riko Yamagishi, and Yumo-chan Kishimoto suddenly change the number of songs and start dancing.
There is a part where the number of songs suddenly changes and we start dancing, and that's where you introduced a little pop genre of dance.
There are a lot of choreographies that we haven't seen in Tsubaki Factory's songs so far.
I hope you will pay attention to them.
At the end of the song, we all wink at each other.
It was hard to find such a cute point that was decided on.
I hope everyone will be moved by it.
Yes, we also performed a song called "Tearful Police Box Drama" at the Hina Fest.
We covered a song called "Nada no Hiroba Koubangeki" (Tears in the Broad Police Box) at the Hina Fest.
I had a hard time learning the dance moves.
I was struggling to learn the dance, and I couldn't remember the choreography for each sentence.
It's not like, "This dance is for the A melody, this dance is for the B melody," but "This dance is for the lyrics.
It was very difficult for me because the dance was based on the meaning of the lyrics.
I remember that it was very difficult for me to memorize the dances.
But this time, skip-skip-skip-skip is also very difficult for me.
There were some parts that I thought it would be difficult for me to memorize.
But as the title says, it's a very cute song that makes you want to skip just by listening to it.
I thought it was a very cute song that made me want to skip just by listening to it.I thought it was a very cute song.
Yes, there is a movement called "skipping" in the choreography.
It's a dance where the sense of movement is very important.
Tsubaki Factory dances this in heels at live performances
I thought it's amazing that Tsubaki Factory dances in heels at live performances.
I thought, "I'm going to train my body sensation, too.
That's all for now. Skip! Skip! dance lesson.
You never know what you're going to do until you try.
It's time for Kisaki Karada and Sakira Ishiyama to say goodbye to UPKAMI!
We've seen a lot of different videos this time.
I was impressed by Tsubaki Factory's "Skip-skip-skip" dance lesson.
I was so impressed by the twists and turns, which I wouldn't normally notice.
They were so detailed and particular about things that you wouldn't normally notice.
I would like to see it again in a music video or something.
I was really impressed by the video of Beyonce's music video for "One in the night sky where you can't even draw a dream".
I personally love this song, so I was very happy to be able to see the music video shoot.
In UpCami, we will go behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the UpFront Group.
Please subscribe to our channel to get a glimpse of what you don't normally see!
This time upcami will be with Kisaki Karahata of JuiceJuice and
and Sakura Ishiyama of JuiceJuice.
Good bye!
Next time on Akukami
Makeup lecture of that member from Ocha-no-Ma
And then
Tsubaki factory dance lesson of "It's not a mistake, we won't cry" will be shown on the website.
Enjoy!
Thank you for watching!